<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-06-28T09:08:52-06:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Creative AML</title><subtitle>Creative AML is an agency for web development and provide a server configuration. In the past we was Solarin Industries but the time were going we did MedicinaResources and now we develop more technologies such Alexa skills.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Creative AML</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/04/05/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Creative AML" /><published>2021-04-05T11:04:06-06:00</published><updated>2021-04-05T11:04:06-06:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/04/05/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/04/05/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;Creative AML was born in 2014 as AML Productions, but then we decided to change that name more creative and not so serious. as you know we love design, but as you can see this post is like some robust and obsolet, but every year we gonna change the concept design don’t worry!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So after complete this project we going to move forward to the first ecommerce web design, where we have a lot of work to do! since install the cloud, a database, concept design, and the development. We plan to end and complete the first big commit at the end of June. We already have some designs from other designers that are very cool to add and of course you will imagine that will be a lot of lines of code only in the design but also for the logic of the online shop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;which-technologies-for-the-online-shop&quot;&gt;Which technologies for the online shop?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We were think about which serve to build for this project, for now we choose NodeJs for the back-end and for the front-end will be VueJs. We like to use NodeJs because is fast for ecommerce sites and for deploying will be at amazon or even at firebase. But will better to deploy using TOR, like a darkEcommerce you know and sell those stuff that are totally illegal and fun XD. Just kidding!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;medicinaresources-again&quot;&gt;MedicinaResources again?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeap! as you know there is a lot of audience that want to see back this website, but we have a plan to reduce cost for tunneling and callbacks for the region, because is too expensive without have any income from this site. One of the is a button for donate and another one is adds. we expect to get earns on this in the first year that will be at 2022. This project will start when we complete our ecommerce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;but-what-is-creative-aml&quot;&gt;But, what is Creative AML?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creative AML is a small startup where we will design AI, new websites, new apps for blockchain, develop apps, create content, create innovation. All this work will be held in Santiago de Guatemala we believe in a new future where the corruption will stop, will be more optimal, advance and better education, more security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this startup has a lot of work to do, and we do not plan to stop, never until see the changes that we describe before.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jorge</name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">Creative AML was born in 2014 as AML Productions, but then we decided to change that name more creative and not so serious. as you know we love design, but as you can see this post is like some robust and obsolet, but every year we gonna change the concept design don’t worry! So after complete this project we going to move forward to the first ecommerce web design, where we have a lot of work to do! since install the cloud, a database, concept design, and the development. We plan to end and complete the first big commit at the end of June. We already have some designs from other designers that are very cool to add and of course you will imagine that will be a lot of lines of code only in the design but also for the logic of the online shop. Which technologies for the online shop? We were think about which serve to build for this project, for now we choose NodeJs for the back-end and for the front-end will be VueJs. We like to use NodeJs because is fast for ecommerce sites and for deploying will be at amazon or even at firebase. But will better to deploy using TOR, like a darkEcommerce you know and sell those stuff that are totally illegal and fun XD. Just kidding! MedicinaResources again? Yeap! as you know there is a lot of audience that want to see back this website, but we have a plan to reduce cost for tunneling and callbacks for the region, because is too expensive without have any income from this site. One of the is a button for donate and another one is adds. we expect to get earns on this in the first year that will be at 2022. This project will start when we complete our ecommerce. But, what is Creative AML? Creative AML is a small startup where we will design AI, new websites, new apps for blockchain, develop apps, create content, create innovation. All this work will be held in Santiago de Guatemala we believe in a new future where the corruption will stop, will be more optimal, advance and better education, more security. So this startup has a lot of work to do, and we do not plan to stop, never until see the changes that we describe before.</summary></entry></feed>